{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "6 * 6 \u003d 36\n-6 * -6 \u003d 36\nThus, the square roots of 36 are 6 and -6.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√36", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "13 * 13 \u003d 169\n-13 * -13 \u003d 169\nThus, the square roots of 169 are 13 and -13.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√169", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "5 * 5 \u003d 25\n-5 * -5 \u003d 25\nThus, the square roots of 25 are 5 and -5.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "3 * 3 * 3 \u003d 27\nThus, the cube root of 27 is 3.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "8 * 8 * 8 \u003d 512\nThus, the cube root of 512 is 8.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "5 * 5 * 5 \u003d 125\nThus, the cube root of 125 is 5.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "11 * 11 \u003d 121\n-11 * -11 \u003d 121\nThus, the square roots of 121 are 11 and -11.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 121", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "-3 * -3 * -3 \u003d -27\nThus, the cube root of -27 is -3.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "6 * 6 * 6 \u003d 216\nThus, the cube root of 216 is 6.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, -10", "explanation": "10 * 10 \u003d 100\n-10 * -10 \u003d 100\nThus, the square roots of 100 are 10 and -10.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 100", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "-2 * -2 * -2 \u003d -8\nThus, the cube root of -8 is -2.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "-9 * -9 * -9 \u003d -729\nThus, the cube root of -729 is -9.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "6 * 6 \u003d 36\n-6 * -6 \u003d 36\nThus, the square roots of 36 are 6 and -6.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√36", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15, -15", "explanation": "15 * 15 \u003d 225\n-15 * -15 \u003d 225\nThus, the square roots of 225 are 15 and -15.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 225", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "9 * 9 * 9 \u003d 729\nThus, the cube root of 729 is 9.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "8 * 8 * 8 \u003d 512\nThus, the cube root of 512 is 8.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "9 * 9 * 9 \u003d 729\nThus, the cube root of 729 is 9.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "4 * 4 \u003d 16\n-4 * -4 \u003d 16\nThus, the square roots of 16 are 4 and -4.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "-5 * -5 * -5 \u003d -125\nThus, the cube root of -125 is -5.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "14 * 14 \u003d 196\n-14 * -14 \u003d 196\nThus, the square roots of 196 are 14 and -14.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√196", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "7 * 7 * 7 \u003d 343\nThus, the cube root of 343 is 7.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12, -12", "explanation": "12 * 12 \u003d 144\n-12 * -12 \u003d 144\nThus, the square roots of 144 are 12 and -12.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√144", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "-5 * -5 * -5 \u003d -125\nThus, the cube root of -125 is -5.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "-3 * -3 * -3 \u003d -27\nThus, the cube root of -27 is -3.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "-2 * -2 * -2 \u003d -8\nThus, the cube root of -8 is -2.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "6 * 6 * 6 \u003d 216\nThus, the cube root of 216 is 6.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "6 * 6 \u003d 36\n-6 * -6 \u003d 36\nThus, the square roots of 36 are 6 and -6.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 36", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "4 * 4 \u003d 16\n-4 * -4 \u003d 16\nThus, the square roots of 16 are 4 and -4.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "11 * 11 \u003d 121\n-11 * -11 \u003d 121\nThus, the square roots of 121 are 11 and -11.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√121", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "-5 * -5 * -5 \u003d -125\nThus, the cube root of -125 is -5.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "14 * 14 \u003d 196\n-14 * -14 \u003d 196\nThus, the square roots of 196 are 14 and -14.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 196", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "-9 * -9 * -9 \u003d -729\nThus, the cube root of -729 is -9.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "5 * 5 \u003d 25\n-5 * -5 \u003d 25\nThus, the square roots of 25 are 5 and -5.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "5 * 5 \u003d 25\n-5 * -5 \u003d 25\nThus, the square roots of 25 are 5 and -5.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "-9 * -9 * -9 \u003d -729\nThus, the cube root of -729 is -9.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "-9 * -9 * -9 \u003d -729\nThus, the cube root of -729 is -9.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "8 * 8 \u003d 64\n-8 * -8 \u003d 64\nThus, the square roots of 64 are 8 and -8.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "6 * 6 \u003d 36\n-6 * -6 \u003d 36\nThus, the square roots of 36 are 6 and -6.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√36", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -7", "explanation": "7 * 7 \u003d 49\n-7 * -7 \u003d 49\nThus, the square roots of 49 are 7 and -7.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√49", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "2 * 2 * 2 \u003d 8\nThus, the cube root of 8 is 2.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "13 * 13 \u003d 169\n-13 * -13 \u003d 169\nThus, the square roots of 169 are 13 and -13.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 169", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "3 * 3 \u003d 9\n-3 * -3 \u003d 9\nThus, the square roots of 9 are 3 and -3.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "3 * 3 * 3 \u003d 27\nThus, the cube root of 27 is 3.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "2 * 2 * 2 \u003d 8\nThus, the cube root of 8 is 2.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "13 * 13 \u003d 169\n-13 * -13 \u003d 169\nThus, the square roots of 169 are 13 and -13.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 169", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "9 * 9 * 9 \u003d 729\nThus, the cube root of 729 is 9.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "8 * 8 \u003d 64\n-8 * -8 \u003d 64\nThus, the square roots of 64 are 8 and -8.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "4 * 4 \u003d 16\n-4 * -4 \u003d 16\nThus, the square roots of 16 are 4 and -4.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "11 * 11 \u003d 121\n-11 * -11 \u003d 121\nThus, the square roots of 121 are 11 and -11.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 121", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "-6 * -6 * -6 \u003d -216\nThus, the cube root of -216 is -6.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "-3 * -3 * -3 \u003d -27\nThus, the cube root of -27 is -3.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "-2 * -2 * -2 \u003d -8\nThus, the cube root of -8 is -2.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "14 * 14 \u003d 196\n-14 * -14 \u003d 196\nThus, the square roots of 196 are 14 and -14.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√196", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12, -12", "explanation": "12 * 12 \u003d 144\n-12 * -12 \u003d 144\nThus, the square roots of 144 are 12 and -12.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 144", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "5 * 5 \u003d 25\n-5 * -5 \u003d 25\nThus, the square roots of 25 are 5 and -5.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "5 * 5 * 5 \u003d 125\nThus, the cube root of 125 is 5.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "14 * 14 \u003d 196\n-14 * -14 \u003d 196\nThus, the square roots of 196 are 14 and -14.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 196", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "7 * 7 * 7 \u003d 343\nThus, the cube root of 343 is 7.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "8 * 8 * 8 \u003d 512\nThus, the cube root of 512 is 8.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "-4 * -4 * -4 \u003d -64\nThus, the cube root of -64 is -4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15, -15", "explanation": "15 * 15 \u003d 225\n-15 * -15 \u003d 225\nThus, the square roots of 225 are 15 and -15.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 225", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "-3 * -3 * -3 \u003d -27\nThus, the cube root of -27 is -3.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d -343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "14 * 14 \u003d 196\n-14 * -14 \u003d 196\nThus, the square roots of 196 are 14 and -14.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√196", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "8 * 8 \u003d 64\n-8 * -8 \u003d 64\nThus, the square roots of 64 are 8 and -8.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "11 * 11 \u003d 121\n-11 * -11 \u003d 121\nThus, the square roots of 121 are 11 and -11.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 121", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "-7 * -7 * -7 \u003d -343\nThus, the cube root of -343 is -7.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "3 * 3 \u003d 9\n-3 * -3 \u003d 9\nThus, the square roots of 9 are 3 and -3.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "-8 * -8 * -8 \u003d -512\nThus, the cube root of -512 is -8.", "question": "Find all the roots:\n^3√-512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "4 * 4 \u003d 16\n-4 * -4 \u003d 16\nThus, the square roots of 16 are 4 and -4.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "question": "Find all the roots:\n√16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "4 * 4 * 4 \u003d 64\nThus, the cube root of 64 is 4.", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^3 \u003d 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "6 * 6 \u003d 36\n-6 * -6 \u003d 36\nThus, the square roots of 36 are 6 and -6.\nDon\u0027t forget about the negative case!", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Find all possible values of x:\nx^2 \u003d 36", "type": "text"}
]}